<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right; margin:10px" width="250" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/Vision_Helpdesk
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/customersupport/Vision_Helpdesk
	</ratings>
	<space>
		13733513
	</space>
	<support>
		http://support.visionhelpdesk.com/
	</support>
	<version>
		3.9.10
	</version>
	<mod>20</mod>
	<release_date>17-09-2014</release_date>
	<admin>manage/</admin>
	<softversion>
		4.1.7
	</softversion>
	<requirement check="php" type="version" operator="ge" value="5.3.0" />
	<requirement check="php" type="version" operator="lt" value="5.4.0" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="curl" />
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">Vision Helpdesk</font> is a Web-Based True Satellite Helpdesk Software that allows you to manage support for Multiple Companies at one place.
		<br /><br />
		With single front-end and each company having its own client portal makes it true satellite helpdesk.
		<br /><br />
		You will need a Valid License key to install and run Vision Helpdesk.
		<br /><br />
		Vision Helpdesk is licensed under their <a href="http://www.thevisionworld.com/company/termsandconditions" target="_blank">Software License Agreement</a>.
		</english-overview>		
		<english-features>
<font size="2" color="#6F8128"><b>Multi Domain / Satellite Helpdesk</b></font><br />
Vision Helpdesk is the only web-based helpdesk software that allows you to manage support for multiple companies at one place. With single front-end and each company having its own client portal makes it true satellite helpdesk.<br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#6F8128"><b>Multi Channel Helpdesk</b></font><br />
The ALL IN ONE customer support helpdesk allows you to manage various channels like E-MAIL, WEB-FORMS, TWITTER, FACEBOOK, CALLS everything under single roof.<br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#6F8128"><b>Online Issue Tracker</b></font><br />
Track issues online, Ticket creation using web interface and Email Parsing. Fetch emails using email piping, POP3, IMAP, POP3 SSL, IMAP SSL. Advance features like Two Way Email Parsing | Catch All Rules | Pre and Post Email parsing | manage Break-Lines<br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#6F8128"><b>Ticket Billing</b></font><br />
Prepaid and Postpaid Billing | Manage Credit | Create Invoice |  Taxation |  Bill Tickets Per Minute | Per Hour| Per Ticket | Per Post, Track Bill Time, Multi-Currency | Automation and much more..<br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#6F8128"><b>Self Help</b></font><br />
Predefined Replies for Staff, Manage Knowledgebase for Clients and Staff, Create Forums, Question and Answer, Bug Submission, Feature Requests, Manage Downloads  and more..<br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#6F8128"><b>Automation</b></font><br />
Work Flow | SLA and Escalations — Automate your tickets work using rule based criteria and decide what action system should take on matching specific criteria conditions. Setup SLA’s and offer timely response to tickets.<br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#6F8128"><b>Blabby</b></font><br />
Private Social Hub for your staff members to communicate, share knowledge | files | presentations | collaborate on ticket issues.<br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#6F8128"><b>Custom Reports</b></font><br />
Build instant custom reports (charts, figures and tables) get insights of your helpdesk, measure and analyze the metrics that are important for your organization.
		</english-features>
		<english-exp_license>You can get free trial license <a href="http://www.visionhelpdesk.com/free-trial" target="_blank">here.</a></english-exp_license>
	</languages>
</soft>